Washington Star 061 061
Stage
- Series 23: Photograph Morgue
  - Sub-Series 1: Biographical
    - Keaton, Lance - Keeton, Kathy (Box 0711)
    - Keaver, Karl - Keith, Francis, W. (Box 0712)
    - Keith, Norman - Keller, Helen (Collective Folders: KEL; KELL) (Box 0713)
    - Keller, Helen - Kellums, Vivien (Collective Folders: KELLEY) (Box 0714)
    - Kelly, Bob - Kelly, Harry, F. (Collective Folders: KELLY) (Box 0715)
    - Kelly, Jack - Kelly, William F. (Collective Folders: KELLY, I-R; KELLY, S-Z) (Box 0716)
    - Kelly, Winfield - Kendall, Donald M. (Collective Folders: KELM, KELT, KEM, KEN, KEND) (Box 0717)
    - Kendall, Donald R. - Kennedy, Caroline (Collective Folders: KENNE) (Box 0718)
    - Kennedy, Caroline - Kennedy, Edward (Box 0719)
    - Kennedy, Edward (1969) - (Convention 1968) (Box 0720)
    - Kennedy, Edward (Dedications - Sen) (Box 0721)
    - Kennedy, Edward (Sen - Visits) (Box 0722)
    - Kennedy, Edward (Voting) - Kennedy, Edward Mrs. (Box 0723)
    - Kennedy, Edward Mrs. - Kennedy, John F. (Box 0724)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Assassination - Award) (Box 0725)
      Needs new box
    - Kennedy, John F. (Assassination and Funeral) (Box 0726)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Baseball - Funeral) (Box 0727)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Funeral - Grave) (Box 0728)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Grave - Painitngs) (Box 0729)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Pets - Speaking) (Box 0730)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Speaking - Visits, M) (Box 0731)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Vists, M - With, B) (Box 0732)
    - Kennedy, John F. (With B-G) (Box 0733)
    - Kennedy, John F. (With G-R) (Box 0734)
    - Kennedy, John F. (With R) - Kennedy, John F. Jr. (Box 0735)
    - Kennedy, Mrs. John F. (General - Visits U) (Box 0736)
    - Kennedy, Mrs. John F. (Visits U - With S) (Box 0737)
    - Kennedy, Mrs. John F. (Wire Service - General) (Box 0738)
    - Kennedy, John, R. - Kennedy, Mrs. Joseph (Box 0739)
    - Kennedy, Joseph, III - Kennedy, Robert F. (Campaign) (Box 0740)
    - Kennedy, Robert F. (Campaign - Family) (Box 0741)
    - Kennedy, Robert F. (Family - Monuments and Memorials) (Box 0742)
    - Kennedy, Robert F. (Monuments and Memorials - Senator) (Box 0743)
    - Kennedy, Robert F. (TV) - Kennedy, Mrs. Robert F. (1971) (Box 0744)
    - Kennedy, Mrs. Robert F. (1971 - With) (Box 0745)
    - Kennedy, Rory - Keny, Leroy (Collective Folders: KENT) (Box 0746)
    - Kenyatta, Charles - Kerr, Clark (Collective Folders: KEO; KER) (Box 0747)
    - Kerr, Edward - Kessler, Melvin (Collective Folders: KERR; KES) (Box 0748)
    - Kestnbau, M. - Khachturian, Aram (Collective Folders: KET; KEY; KEYS; KH) (Box 0749)
    - Kharasch, Shari - Khadafi, Moammar (Collective Folders: KHAN) (Box 0750)
    - Kheel, Theodore - Khrushchev, Nikita (portraits) (Collective Folders: KHO) (Box 0751)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita (Speaking - Visits) (Box 0752)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita (Visits) - Kiba, Steve (Box 0753)
    - Kibbee, Guy - Kierdorf Frank (Collective Folders: KI) (Box 0754)
    - Kierdorf, Herman - Killeen, Edward V. (Collective Folders: KIE) (Box 0755)
    - Kilmuir, Viscount - Kinder, Ellis (Collective Folders: KIL, KIM, KIMB, KIMM) (Box 0756)
    - Kindle, Greg - King Don (Collective Folders: KING, C) (Box 0757)
    - King, Edward J. - King, Martin Luther, Jr.(1965) (Collective Folders: KING, E; KING, F; KING, G; KING, H; KING, L) (Box 0758)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr. (1966 - Memorials) (Box 0759)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr. (Memorials) - King, Mrs. Martin Luther, Jr. (Box 0760)
    - King, Mary - King, Yolanda (Collective Folders: KING, M; KING, N; KING,O; KING, Q; KING, R; KING, V; KING, W; KING, U) (Box 0761)
    - Kingdon, Dr. Frank - Kinski, Natassia (Collective Folders: KINGS; KIN; KINN) (Box 0762)
    - Kinsolving, Lee - Kirk, Lisa (Collective Folders: KIP; KIR; KIRBY; KIRK; KIRK (A-I)) (Box 0763)
    - Kirk, Norman - Kislenko, LT GEN (Collective Folders: KIRK, P; KIS: KIRK, W; KIRS) (Box 0764)
    - Kisley, Steve - Kissinger, Henry (Collective Folders: KISS) (Box 0765)
    - Kissinger, Henry (General - Pets) (Box 0766)
    - Kissinger, Henry (Portraits - Visits, General) (Box 0767)
    - Kissinger, Henry (Visits, Africa - Middle East) (Box 0768)
    - Kissenger, Henry (Visits, Middle East - With, Groups) (Box 0769)
    - Kissenger, Henry (With, H - Wife) (Box 0770)
    - Kissinger, Henry (With, Wife) - Klassen, Elmer (Collective Folders: KIST; KIT; KL) (Box 0771)
    - Klaus; Billy - Kleinwaechter, Ludwig (Collective Folders: KLE; KLEIN) (Box 0772)
    - Klem, Bill - Kluszewski, Ted (Collective Folders: KLI; KLU) (Box 0773)
    - Klutz, Clyde - Knight, John S. (Collective Folders: KM; KNIGHT, A-Z) (Box 0774)
    - Knight, John S. - Knull, Kenneth (Collective Folders: KNO; KNU) (Box 0775)
    - Knussen, Oliver - Kohler, Foy D. (Collective Folders: KO; KOB; KOC; KOE; KOH) (Box 0776)
    - Kohler, Herbert V. - Konvitz, Jeffrey (Collective Folders: KOL; KOM; KON) (Box 0777)
    - Koo, Wellington - Korman, Milton (Collective Folders: KOO; KOP; KOR) (Box 0778)
    - Korman, Peter - Kosygin, Alexei (Collective Folders: KOS) (Box 0779)
    - Kosygin, Alexei - Kotsonis, Ieronimos (Collective Folders: KOT) (Box 0780)
    - Kotto, Yaphet - Kraft, Jack (Collective Folders: KOZ; KR) (Box 0781)
    - Kraft, Joseph - Kratzert, Bill (Collective Folders: KRAF; KRAM; KRAN; KRAS) (Box 0782)
    - Kraus, Alvin E. - Krenz, Eric (Collective Folders: KRAU; KRAV; KRE; KREI) (Box 0783)
    - Krepfle, Keith - Krogh, Egil (Collective Folders: KRES; KRI; KRO) (Box 0784)
    - Krol, John Joseph - Krumm, Philip O. (Collective Folders: KROG; KROL: KROU; KRU; KRUM) (Box 0785)
    - Krupa, Gene - Kuehn, Philip G (Collective Folders: KRUZ; KU) (Box 0786)
    - Kuenn, Harvey - Kunstler, William M. (Collective Folders: KUG; KUH; KUL; KUM; KUN) (Box 0787)
    - Kunstler, William - Kuusinen, Hertta (Collective Folders: KUR; KUS; KUT) (Box 0788)
    - Kuusinen, Otto - Ky, Nguyen Cao (Collective Folders: KUZ; KW; KY) (Box 0789)
    - Ky, Mrs. Nguyen Cao - LaCock, Pete (Collective Folders: L; LAB) (Box 0790)
    - LaCoss, Mike - Lagaillarde, Pierre (Collective Folders: LAF; LAG) (Box 0791)
    - LaGarde, Tom - Laird, Melvin (Collective Folders: LAH; LAI) (Box 0792)
    - Laird, Melvin - Lais, Alberto (Box 0793)
    - Laise, Carol - Lamarre, Bleriot H. (Collective Folders: LAK; LAL; LAM) (Box 0794)
    - Lamason, David - Lampron, Gerry (Collective Folders: LAMB; LAMBERT; LAMP) (Box 0795)
    - Lancaster, Burt - Lanchester, Elsa (Collective Folders: LAN) (Box 0796)
    - Landers, Ann - Landon, Michael (Collective Folders: LAND) (Box 0797)
    - Landon, Paul - Lane, Thomas (Collective Folders: LANDR; LANE, A.I.; LANE, J.; LANE, S-Z) (Box 0798)
    - Lane, Thomas - Langer, William (Collective Folders: LANG; LANG, A-Z; LANGE) (Box 0799)
    - Langford, Albert E. - Lantaff, William (Collective Folders: LANGL; LANI; LANS) (Box 0800)
    - Lantz, Walter - Lara, Guillermo (Collective Folders: LAO; LAP; LAR) (Box 0801)
    - Laraki, Moulay Ahmed - Larsen, Swen A (Collective Folders: LARA; LARI; LARK; LARO; LARR; LARSEN; LARSON) (Box 0802)
    - Larson, Arthur - Lassiter, Olbert (Collective Folders: LARU; LAS; LASS) (Box 0803)
    - Lastarza, Roland - Laughlin, Tom (Collective Folders: LAT; LATH; LATI; LATT; LAU) (Box 0804)
    - Laughna, Mike, - Lavin, Linda (Collective Folders: LAUG; LAV) (Box 0805)
    - Lavine, Elizabeth - Lawrence, Robert (Collective Folders: LAWL; LAWRENCE, A; LAWRENCE, I-R) (Box 0806)
    - Lawrence, Ralph P. - Layden, Elmer (Collective Folders: LAWRENCE, S-Z; LAWS; LAWSON; LAWT; LAY) (Box 0807)
      Std MS
    - Laye, Evelyn - Leach, William S. (Collective Folders: LAYN; LAYT; LAZ; LEA; LEACH) (Box 0808)
    - Leachman, Cloris - Lear, William P. (Collective Folders: LEAHY; LEAR) (Box 0809)
    - Learned, Michael - Lechner, Ira M. (Collective Folders: LEB; LEC) (Box 0810)
    - Lechoco, Napoleon - Lee, Blair III (Collective Folders: LED; LEE) (Box 0811)
    - Lee III, Blair - Lee, Lena (Collective Folders: LEE, J-R) (Box 0812)
    - Lee, Leron - Leeper (Collective Folders: LEE, S-Z; LEES) (Box 0813)
    - Leewaye - Lei (Collective Folders: LEET; LEF; LEG; LEI) (Box 0814)
    - Leiding - Lejuene (Collective Folders: LEIG; LEH; LEIT; LEL) (Box 0815)
    - Leland - Lemnitzer (Collective Folders: LEM; LEMN) (Box 0816)
    - Lemon - Lennon, S (Collective Folders: LEN) (Box 0817)
    - Lennon, W. - Leonard, Sugar Ray (Collective Folders: LEO; LEON; LEONARD) (Box 0818)
    - Leonard, Sugar Ray - Lerch, Henry (Collective Folders: LEP; LER) (Box 0819)
    - Lerch, Randy - Leseur (Collective Folders: LEROY; LES; LESS; LEST) (Box 0820)
    - Letelier - Levesque (Collective Folders: LET; LEU; LEV; LEVI) (Box 0821)
    - Levi, Julian - Levy, Albert (Box 0822)
    - Levi, Bernard - Lewis, Edward (Collective Folders: LEW; LEWIS, A-J) (Box 0823)
    - Lewis, Fulton - Lewis, John T. (Collective Folders: LEWIS, J-R) (Box 0824)
    - Lewis, Judy - Li, Ch (Collective Folders: LEWIS, S-Z; LI) (Box 0825)
    - Li, CP - Liddy, G Gordon (Collective Folders: LIB; LID) (Box 0826)
    - Liddy, G. Gordon - Lilienthal, A. (Collective Folders: LIE; LIG; LIL) (Box 0827)
    - Lilienthal, D. - Lincoln, Abraham (Collective Folders: LIM; LINC) (Box 0828)
    - Lincoln, Abraham - Lindberg, J. (Collective Folders: LIND; LIND, A-Z) (Box 0829)
    - Lindberg, - Linden, H. (Collective Folders: LINDE) (Box 0830)
    - Linder - Lindsay, John V. (Collective Folders: LINDL) (Box 0831)
    - Lindsay, John V. - Lingo, Al (Collective Folders: LINDSEY; LINE) (Box 0832)
    - Lingo, Ted - Liotta (Collective Folders: LING; LINK; LINN; LINT) (Box 0833)
    - Lipchitz - List (Collective Folders: LIP; LIPP; LIPS; LIS) (Box 0834)
    - Lister - Littleton (Collective Folders: LIT; LITTLE) (Box 0835)
    - Littlewood - Llewellyn, J. (Collective Folders: LIV; LLLE) (Box 0836)
    - Llewellyn, R. - Loche (Collective Folders: LLO; LO; LOB; LOC; LOCK) (Box 0837)
    - Locke, E. - Lodge, HC (Collective Folders: LOD) (Box 0838)
    - Lodge, HC - Lofstrand (Collective Folders: LOE; LOF) (Box 0839)
    - Lofthouse, - Lohrke (Collective Folders: LOH) (Box 0840)
    - Lollobrigida - Lombardo, G. (Collective Folders: LOI; LOM) (Box 0841)
    - Lombardo, M. - Long, Huey (Collective Folders: LONG, A-I; LON) (Box 0842)
    - Long, J. - Longridge (Collective Folders: LONG, J-R; LONG, S-Z; LONGS) (Box 0843)
    - Longsreet - Lopez, Jose Portillo (Collective Folders: LOO; LOPEZ) (Box 0844)
    - Lopez, Jose Portillo - Loren, Sophia (Collective Folders: LOR; LORD) (Box 0845)
    - Loren, Sophia - Lougherty (Collective Folders: LOS; LOT; LOU) (Box 0846)
    - Lougery - Lovelace (Collective Folders: LOV; LOVE) (Box 0847)
    - Loveless - Lowe, J. (Collective Folders: LOW) (Box 0848)
    - Lowe, J. - Lubore (Collective Folders: LOZ; LOU; LUB; LUC) (Box 0849)
    - Lucan - Luce, CB (Collective Folders: LUCE) (Box 0850)
    - Luce, D. - Ludendorf (Collective Folders: LUD) (Box 0851)
    - Luder - Lukens (Collective Folders: LUE; LEG; LEK) (Box 0852)
    - Lule - Lupica (Collective Folders: LUM: LUN; LUND; LUP) (Box 0853)
    - Lupien - Luxemourg Royal Family (Collective Folders: LUR; LUS; LUT) (Box 0854)
    - Luxembourg Royal Family - Lynch, A. (Collective Folders: LY; LYL; LYN; LYNCH) (Box 0855)
    - Lynch, C. - Lynn, R. Matthew (Collective Folders: LYNN) (Box 0856)
    - Lynne - Lywen (Collective Folders: LYON; LYONS; LYS; LYT) (Box 0857)
    - Maas - MacArow (Collective Folders: M; MAC; MACA) (Box 0858)
    - MacArthur - McArthur, Gen (Box 0859)
    - MacArthur - Macready (Collective Folders: MACB; MACC) (Box 0860)
    - MacDonald - MacGregor (Collective Folders: MACD; MACE; MACF; MACG) (Box 0861)
    - MacHacek - Mackenzie, G. (Collective Folders: MACH; MACI; MACK) (Box 0862)
    - Mackenzie, J. - Macleish (Collective Folders: MACL) (Box 0863)
    - MacLeon - MacNIder (Collective Folders: MACM; MACN) (Box 0864)
    - MacNell - Maddox, J. (Collective Folders: MACP; MACO; MACR; MAD; MADI) (Box 0865)
    - Maddox, Lester - Maestas (Collective Folders: MAE; MAG) (Box 0866)
    - Magalhaes - Mahaffey, A. (Collective Folders: MAH) (Box 0867)
    - Mahaffey, J. - Mailer (Collective Folders: MAHO; MAHI) (Box 0868)
    - Mailliard - Maksoud (Collective Folders: MAJ; MAK) (Box 0869)
    - Malagodi - Malin (Collective Folders: MAL; MALA; MALE; MALI) (Box 0870)
    - Malinchak - Maloney, E. (Collective Folders: MALL; MALLE; MALLO; MALO; MALONE; MALONEY) (Box 0871)
    - Maloney, Jack - Mandel, M (Collective Folders: MAM; MAN; MAND) (Box 0872)
    - Mandel, Marvin (Box 0873)
    - Mandel, Marv (Mrs.) - Manley (Collective Folders: MANG) (Box 0874)
    - Mann - Manning, M. (Collective Folders: MANN) (Box 0875)
    - Manning, R. - Mansfield, M (Collective Folders: MANO; MANS) (Box 0876)
    - Mansfield, R. - Mao, Tsetung (Collective Folders: MANU) (Box 0877)
    - Mao, Tsetung - March, F. (Collective Folders: MAP; MAR; MARB; MARC; MARCH) (Box 0878)
    - March, H. - Marev (Collective Folders: MARCUS; MARD) (Box 0879)
    - Margai - Markevitch (Collective Folders: MARG; MARI; MARK) (Box 0880)
    - Markeu - Markquand (Collective Folders: MARL; MARKS; MARO; MARQ) (Box 0881)
    - Marques - Marshal (Collective Folders: MARR; MARS; MARSH) (Box 0882)
    - Marshall, A - Marshall, General George (Collective Folders: MARSHALL, A-I) (Box 0883)
    - Marshall, General George - Marshall, Sara (Collective Folders: MARSHALL, J-R; MARSHALL, S-Z) (Box 0884)
    - Marshall, T. - Martin, B. (Collective Folders: MART; MARTIN; MARTIN, A; MARTIN, B) (Box 0885)
    - Martin, C. - Martin, G. (Collective Folders: MARTIN, C; MARTIN, D; MARTIN, E; MARTIN, F; MARTIN, G) (Box 0886)
    - Martin, H. - Martin, O. (Collective Folders: MARTIN, H; MARTIN, J; MARTIN, M; MARTIN, O) (Box 0887)
    - Martin, P. - Martindale (Collective Folders: MARTIN, P; MARTIN, Q; MARTIN, R; Martin, S; MARTIN, T; MARTIN, W; MARTIN, V; MARTIN, XYZ) (Box 0888)
    - Martineau - Marx, Groucho (Collective Folders: MARX) (Box 0889)
    - Marx, Karl - Mason, L. (Collective Folders: MARZ; MAS; MASON, A-I; MASON, J-R) (Box 0890)
    - Mason, M. - Massey (Collective Folders: MASON, S-Z; MASS) (Box 0891)
    - Massie - Mathers (Collective Folders: MAST; MAT; MATHE) (Box 0892)
    - Matheson - Mathieu (Collective Folders: MATHEWS; MATHI) (Box 0893)
    - Mathis - Matthes (Collective Folders: MATHIS; MATS; MATT) (Box 0894)
    - Matthews - Matuszak (Collective Folders: MATTHEWS; MATTI; MATU) (Box 0895)
    - Matz - Max (Collective Folders: MAU; MAV; MAW; MAX) (Box 0896)
    - Maxcy - May (Collective Folders: MAY) (Box 0897)
    - Maye - Mayo (Collective Folders: MAYE; MAYF; MAYN; MAYO) (Box 0898)
    - Mayobre - Mbumba (Collective Folders: MAYS; MAZ) (Box 0899)
    - McAdoo - McBride, M. (Collective Folders: MC; MCA; MCB) (Box 0900)
    - McBride, P. - McCallum, D. (Collective Folders: MCC; MCCAL) (Box 0901)
    - McCallum, P. - McCarthy, Eugene (Collective Folders: MCCAN; MCCAR) (Box 0902)
    - McCarthy, Eugene (Box 0903)
    - McCarthy, Eugene - McCarthy, Joseph (Box 0904)
    - McCarthey, Joseph - McChesney (Collective Folders: MCCL) (Box 0905)
    - McClanahan - McClure, C. (Box 0906)
    - McClure, D - McCord, G. (Collective Folders: MCCOR) (Box 0907)
    - McCord, J. - McCormick, E. (Box 0908)
    - McCormick, E. - McCraw (Collective Folders: MCCOY; MCCR) (Box 0909)
    - McCray - McDermott (Collective Folders: MCCU; MCD) (Box 0910)
    - McDevitt - McDonald, Ed (Collective Folders: MCDO; MCDONALD) (Box 0911)
    - McDonald, G. - McEaddy (Collective Folders: MCE) (Box 0912)
    - McElhenny - McGavin (Collective Folders: MCF; MCG) (Box 0913)
    - McGee - McGonigle (Collective Folders: MCGEE; MCGI; MCGO) (Box 0914)
    - McGolian - McGovern, George (Box 0915)
    - McGovern - George (Box 0916)
    - McGovern - George (Box 0917)
    - McGovern, George - McGowin (Collective Folders: MCGR) (Box 0918)
    - McGrady - McGuire, M. (Collective Folders: MCGU) (Box 0919)
    - McGuire, P. - McIntyre, T. (Collective Folders: MCI) (Box 0920)
    - McIver - McKeldin (Collective Folders: MCKE) (Box 0921)
    - McKellan - McKerrow (Collective Folders: MCKEN; MCKEO) (Box 0922)
    - McKevitt - McLain, Denny (Collective Folders: MCKI; MCKN; MCL) (Box 0923)
    - McLain, Denny - McLeigh (Collective Folders: MCLAU; MCLE) (Box 0924)
    - McLellan - McManus, S. (Collective Folders: MCLO; MCM) (Box 0925)
    - McManus, W - McNally (Collective Folders: MCMI; MCMU; MCN) (Box 0926)
    - McNamara, Andrew, McNamara, Robert (Box 0927)
    - McNamee, McQueen, S. (Collective Folders: MCNE; MCNI; MCO; MCP; MCQ) (Box 0928)
    - McQuilken - Meacham (Collective Folders: MCS; MCT; MCV; MCW; ME) (Box 0929)
    - Mead, Ann-Meany, George (Box 0930)
    - Meara, Anne-Medley, Joseph (Collective Folders: MEC; MED) (Box 0931)
    - Medlin, Clarence-Meir, Golda (Collective Folders: MEE; MEG; MEH; MEI) (Box 0932)
    - Meir, Golda-Mellon, Karen (Collective Folders: MEL; MELE; MELI; MELL; MELLON) (Box 0933)
    - Mellon, Paul-Mendes, Sergio (Collective Folders: MELN; MELO; MELT; MELV; MEM; MEN; MEND) (Box 0934)
    - Mendes-France, Pierre- Menzies, Robert (Box 0935)
    - Meouchi, Page-Meredith, Madge (Collective Folders: MER; MERC; MERE) (Box 0936)
    - Meretskov, Marshal-Merrill, Gary (Collective Folders: MERR) (Box 0937)
    - Merrill, Gretchen-Mesta, Perle (Collective Folders: MES; MESS) (Box 0938)
    - Mesta, Perle-Meyer, Sylvia (Collective Folders: MET; MEY; MEYER) (Box 0939)
    - Meyer, William-Michaels, Walt (Collective Folders: MEYERS; MI; MICH) (Box 0940)
    - Michalek, Louis-Mihajlov, Mihajlo (Collective Folders: MICK; MID; MIE; MIH) (Box 0941)
    - Mihalic, Johnny-Miles, Sarah (Collective Folders: MIK; MILES) (Box 0942)
    - Miles, Sylvia-Miller, Arthur L. (Collective Folders: MILL; MILLER, A.) (Box 0943)
    - Miller, B.-Miller, F. Don (Collective Folders: MILLER, B.; MILLER, C.; MILLER, D.; MILLER, E.; MILLER F.) (Box 0944)
    - Miller, G.-Miller, Jody (Collective Folders: MILLER, H.; MILLER, I.; MILLER, J.) (Box 0945)
    - Miller, John-Miller, Ron (Collective Folders: MILLER, K.; MILLER, L.; MILLER, M.; MILLER, N.; MILLER, O.; MILLER, P.; MILLER, R.) (Box 0946)
    - Miller, S.-Millns, Jim (Collective Folders: MILLER, S.; MILLER, T.; MILLER V.; MILLER, W.; MILLER, XYZ; MILLI) (Box 0947)
    - Mills-Millner, John (Collective Folders: MILLS) (Box 0948)
    - Milner, Martin-Minichello, Raphael (Collective Folders: MIM; MIN) (Box 0949)
    - Minish, Joseph-Miron, Ray (Collective Folders: MIR) (Box 0950)
    - Mis-Mitchell, Mrs. Howard (Collective Folders: MIS; MIT; MITCHELL, A.-I.) (Box 0951)
    - Mitchell, J.-Mitchell, John (Collective Folders: MITCHELL, J.-R.) (Box 0952)
    - Mitchell, John-Mitchell, Stephen (Collective Folders: MITCHELL, S.-Z.) (Box 0953)
    - Mitchell, Theo-Moch, Jules (Collective Folders: MITCHUM; MITE; MIX; MIY; MIZ; ML; MO) (Box 0954)
    - Mock, Edward-Mollenhoff, Clark (Collective Folders: MOH; MOL) (Box 0955)
    - Mollet, Guy-Monaco Royal Family (Collective Folders: MON; MONA) (Box 0956)
    - Monaco Royal Family-Mondale, Walter (Box 0957)
    - Mondale, Walter-Monet, Claude (Collective Folders: MONE) (Box 0958)
    - Mones, Marvin-Montand, Yves (Collective Folders: MONROE; MONS; MONT) (Box 0959)
    - Montanez, Willie-Montoya, Carlos (Collective Folders: MONTGOMERY) (Box 0960)
    - Montoya, Joseph-Moore, Archie (Collective Folders: MOO; MOOR; MOORE, A.) (Box 0961)
    - Moore, Audrey-Moore, George (Collective Folders: MOORE, B.; MOORE, C.; MOORE, D.; MOORE, E.; MOORE, F.; MOORE, G.) (Box 0962)
    - Moore, Gracie-Moore, Nicole (Collective Folders: MOORE, H.; MOORE, I.; MOORE, J.; MOORE, K.; MOORE, L.; MOORE, M.; MOORE, N.) (Box 0963)
    - Moore, O.-Moore, William L. (Collective Folders: MOORE, O.; MOORE, P.; MOORE, Q.; MOORE, R.; MOORE, S.; MOORE, T.; MOORE, U.; MOORE, V.; MOORE, W.) (Box 0964)
    - Moorehead - Moravia (Collective Folders: MOOREH; MORAN) (Box 0965)
    - Mor-Morgan, Helen (Collective Folders: MOR; MORE; MORG; MORGAN, A.-I.) (Box 0966)
    - Morgan, Henry - Morhouse, L. Judson (Collective Folders: MORGAN, J.-R.; MORGAN, S.-Z; MORI) (Box 0967)
    - Morial, Ernest - Morocco, Royal Family (Box 0968)
    - Morocco, Royal Family - Morris, Thomas D. (Collective Folders: MORR; MORRIS, A-I; MORRIS, J.-R.; MORRIS, S-Z) (Box 0969)
    - Morris, Viola - Morsch, Lucile (Collective Folders: MORRISON; MORROW; MORS; MORSE) (Box 0970)
    - Morse, Clarence G - Morton, Thurston (Sen) (Collective Folders: MORT) (Box 0971)
    - Mosbacher, Emil - Moses, Rick (Collective Folders: MOS; MOSER) (Box 0972)
    - Moses, Robert - Moss, William (Collective Folders: MOSS) (Box 0973)
    - Mossadegh, F. Mohammed - Motta, Dick (Collective Folders: MOST; MOT) (Box 0974)
    - Motte, Claire - Moyers, Bill (Collective Folders: MOU; MOW) (Box 0975)
    - Moynihan Daniel P - MRKVA Frank John State Department (Collective Folders: MOY; MRT) (Box 0976)
    - Muccio, John J. - Muirhead, Robert (Collective Folders: MUE) (Box 0977)
    - Mulamba, Leonard - Mullin, Pat (Collective Folders: MUL) (Box 0978)
    - Mullin, Sue - Mumy, Billy (Collective Folders: MULL; MUM; MUN) (Box 0979)
    - Muncey, Bill - Munsel, Patrice (Box 0980)
    - Munsey, Everard - Murphy, Ben (Collective Folders: MUR; MURPHY, A-I) (Box 0981)
    - Murphy, Betty - Murphy, Mark (Box 0982)
    - Murphy, Mary - Murphy, William (Collective Folders: MURPHY, S-Z; MURR) (Box 0983)
    - Murray, Anne - Murray, The K (Collective Folders: MURRAY, A-I; MURRAY, J-R) (Box 0984)
    - Murray, William and Susan - Music, Lorenzo (Collective Folders: Murray, S-Z) (Box 0985)
    - Muskie, Edmund (1971-Portraits) (Box 0986)
    - Muskie, Edmund (Press Conferences - With) - Muskie, Josephine (Box 0987)
    - Musolino - Muzorewa (Collective Folders: MUT; MY; MUSS) (Box 0988)
    - My, Hunh Than - Nabokov, Vladimir (Collective Folders: MYERS; N; NA; NAB) (Box 0989)
    - Nabors - Nagano (Collective Folders: NAD) (Box 0990)
    - Nagel - NAM (Collective Folders: NAG; NAI; NAL; NAM) (Box 0991)
    - Namath - Nannes (Box 0992)
    - Nansen - Nasser, Abdel Hamir (Collective Folders: NAN; NAP; NAR; NASH; NAS) (Box 0993)
    - Nasser, Gamer Abdel - Nathan (Collective Folders: NAT) (Box 0994)
    - Nation - NE (Collective Folders: NAU; NAV; NAY; NAZ) (Box 0995)
    - Ne Win - Nees (Collective Folders: NEE) (Box 0996)
    - Nefertiti - NEL (Collective Folders: NEF; NEI) (Box 0997)
    - Nelson - Nelson, Phil (Collective Folders: NELSON, A-I) (Box 0998)
    - Nelson, Ralph - Neprozhniy (Collective Folders: NELSON, J-R; NELSON, S-Z; NEM) (Box 0999)
    - Neri - Netherlands, Royal Family (Collective Folders: NES) (Box 1000)
    - Netherlands, Royal Family - Neulander (Collective Folders: NEU) (Box 1001)
    - Neuman - Newbold (Collective Folders: NEV; NEW) (Box 1002)
    - Newcomb - Newman, Barry (Collective Folders: NEWM) (Box 1003)
    - Newman, Constance - Newman, Paul (Box 1004)
    - Newman, Ralph - Newton-John, Olivia (Box 1005)
    - New York Rock and Roll - Nicholas, Connie (Collective Folders: NI; NICH) (Box 1006)
    - Nichoalas, Denise - Nicholson, Timothy (Collective Folders: NICHOLS; NICHOLSON) (Box 1007)
    - Nickel - Nico (Collective Folders: NICK; NIDETCH) (Box 1008)
    - Niebuhr - Nikula (Collective Folders: NIE; NIK) (Box 1009)
    - Nilsson - Nipp (Collective Folders: NIL) (Box 1010)
    - Nirenberg - Nixon, Julie (Box 1011)
    - Nixon - Marian - Nixon, Patricia (Box 1012)
    - Nixon, Patricia (with Groups) - Nixon, Patricia (Working) (Box 1013)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Birthdays) - Nixon, Richard M. (Campaign for President) (Box 1014)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Birthdays) - Nixon, Richard M. (Campaign for President) - Nixon, Richard M. (Churchgoing) (Box 1015)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (General) - Nixon, Mrs. Richard M. (Box 1016)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Health) - Nixon, Richard M. (Inaugural) (Box 1017)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Inaugural) - Nixon, Richard M. (Offices) (Box 1018)